<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Burger Recipe</string>
    <string name="Burger_peanut_Recipe">

    1 tablespoon vegetable oil, plus more for brushing \n
    1 onion, finely chopped \n
    2 tablespoons minced fresh ginger \n
    2 garlic cloves, minced \n
    1 cup tomato puree \n
    2 tablespoons ketchup \n
    1 tablespoon red wine vinegar \n
    1 tablespoon Worcestershire sauce \n
    1 1/2 tablespoons Dijon mustard \n
    2 tablespoons honey \n
    2 tablespoons molasses \n
    3 tablespoons pure ancho chile powder \n
    1 canned chipotle in adobo, minced \n
    1/2 cup water \n
    2 tablespoons creamy peanut butter \n
    Salt and freshly ground pepper \n
    4 hamburger buns, split \n
    1 1/2 pounds ground beef chuck \n
    1/2 cup shredded cheddar (3 ounces) \n
    1 scallion, finely chopped \n
    Lettuce and tomato slices, for serving \n

    </string>

    <string name="Burger_peanut_how">
        In a medium saucepan, heat the 1 tablespoon of oil. \n
        Add the onion and ginger and cook over moderate heat, stirring occasionally, until softened, about 5 minutes. \n
        Add the garlic and cook for 1 minute, stirring. \n
        Add the tomato puree, ketchup, vinegar, Worcestershire sauce, mustard, honey, molasses, ancho chile powder, chipotle and water. \n
        Bring to a simmer and cook over low heat, stirring occasionally, until thickened, about 30 minutes. \n
        Transfer the sauce to a blender. Add the peanut butter and puree until smooth. Season the barbecue sauce with salt and pepper. \n
    </string>

    <string name="umami_ing">
    1 cup ruby port \n
    2 pounds mixed ground beef brisket, skirt steak and sirloin steak (20 percent fat) \n
    Salt and freshly ground pepper \n
    1/2 cup Stilton cheese (3 ounces), softened \n
    Umami dust, for sprinkling (optional, see Note) \n
    4 brioche hamburger buns, buttered and toasted \n
    </string>

    <string name="umami_how">
        In a small saucepan, cook the port over moderate heat until reduced to 2 tablespoons, about 15 minutes.
        \n Heat a cast-iron griddle until very hot.
        \n Form the meat into four 4-by-1-inch patties without packing too tightly.
        \n Season generously with salt and pepper.
        \n Arrange the patties on the griddle, cover with a roasting pan and cook over moderately high heat for 4 minutes,
        \n until very crusty.
        \n Flip the patties and cook, covered, for 2 minutes longer; top with the Stilton and cook uncovered for 1 minute.
        \n Transfer the patties to a plate and sprinkle with the umami dust, let rest for 2 minutes and set on the buns.
        \n Drizzle with the reduced port, top with the buns and serve.
    </string>
    
    <string name="pug_burger_ing">

    \n 2 pounds lean ground sirloin
    \n 8 strips applewood-smoked bacon
    \n 1/2 cup mayonnaise, plus more for serving
    \n 1 garlic clove, minced
    \n Kosher salt and freshly ground pepper
    \n 4 kaiser rolls, split
    \n 3 tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil
    \n 3 ounces Danish blue cheese, sliced
    \n Sliced ripe Hass avocado
    \n Bibb lettuce leaves
    \n Red onion slices

    </string>

    <string name="pug_burger_how">
        \n Light a grill.
        \n Form the meat into 4 large patties about 1 inch thick.
        \n Let stand at room temperature for 30 minutes.
        \n In a skillet, cook the bacon over moderate heat until crisp, 6 minutes; drain on paper towels.
        \n In a bowl, mix the 1/2 cup of mayonnaise with the garlic; season with salt and pepper.
        \n Brush the cut sides of the rolls with 2 tablespoons of the oil and lightly toast on the grill.
        \n Brush the burgers with the remaining oil and season well with salt and pepper.
        \n Grill over moderately high heat for 3 minutes; flip and top with the cheese.
        \n Cook for 3 more minutes for medium-rare.
        \n Spread the bottom roll halves with the garlic mayonnaise.
        \n Top with a burger, bacon, avocado, lettuce and onion and serve.
    </string>

    <string name="entry_text_hint">Text to be translated</string>
    <string name="result_text_hint">Translated text</string>
    <string name="speech_button_hint">Text to Speech</string>
    <string name="alert_dialog_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="alert_dialog_close">Close Application</string>
    <string name="error_title_default">Error in WatsonBahasa</string>
    <string name="error_title_invalid_credentials_speech">Invalid Watson Speech Credentials</string>
    <string name="error_title_invalid_credentials_translator">Invalid Watson Translator Credentials</string>
    <string name="error_message_invalid_credentials_translator">Please verify your credentials in \"values/watson_credentials\" and rebuild the application.\n\nSee the README for further assistance.</string>
    <string name="error_message_invalid_credentials_speech">Please verify your credentials in \"values/watson_credentials\" and rebuild the application or continue with no Text To Speech.\n\nSee the README for further assistance.</string>
    <string name="error_title_bluemix_connection">Failed to Connect to Bluemix</string>
    <string name="error_message_bluemix_connection">Please verify your connection to the internet.\n\nSee the README for further assistance.</string>


</resources>
